

CONTACT

07085936545

asorchris2019@gmail.com

© asor_chris

SKILLS

Flyer Design

Logo Design

Brand Identity Design

UI/UX Design

TOOLS

Corel Draw

Photoshop

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

Asor Christopher

Creative Designer

PROFILE

I am a creative designer who tells stories using designs. I help brands design functional and aesthetically pleasing designs and interfaces that communicates the brand's principles and visions.

With my years of experience and attention to details, I've been able to help several businesses scale up through the use of outstanding visuals. I'm a great team player and would be a great addition to any team

EDUCATION

Comprehensive Development Secondary School, Owerri 2012 - 2018

Federal Univeesity of Technoogy, Owerri 2019 - Present

EXPERIENCE

Triple C - Lead Graphic Designer

May 2022 - Present

Agacy Inc - UI/UX Designer

November 2023 - Present

HOBBIES

- Photography
- Reading
- Traveling
- Networking